Finding Aid for the UNITE HERE Records LSC.2325
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Local 11 Records, 1952-2013; 1980-2012
  - Subseries 1.3: Tom Walsh files, circa 1970s-circa 2004
    - Immigration conference, (2000) (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Interest-Based Problem Solving workshop participant's manual, (undated) (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Justice for Janitors, (1995-1999) (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Las Vegas organizing pamphlet, (undated) (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Latino Democrats health and welfare release forms, (2001) (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Leave of Absence (LOA intern training), (undated) (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Letter from Miguel Contreras, (2001 Jul 25) (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Local 11 contracts and pamphlets, (1980s-1990s) (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Local 11 flyers and ephemera, (1975, 1980s, 1990s) (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Local 11 news calendars, (late 1970s, 1981 Dec) (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Local 11 news (newspapers and flyers), (1975, 1989, 1990s) (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Local 11 newsletter (English and Spanish), (1997 Fall) (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Local 11 organizing coordination, (early 1990s) (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Local 11 pamphlets, (2000s) (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Local 11 special meetings attendance sheets, (1990-1991) (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Miramar fired engineers, (undated) (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Miramar vs police, (1999) (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - National Organizing Team photo and article re: union organizing, (1985 May, 1986 Jan) (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - New Otani, (1990s) (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - News clippings (2 folders), (1989-2002) (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
    - Organizer's Resource Guide to the Catholic Perspective on Union Organizing (An), (1991 Dec) (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Political education articles and ephemera, (undated) (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Pomona College food service workers buttons (17= 17 workers fired), (undated) (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Reading materials re: labor history, collective bargaining, and the hotel and restaurant industry, (1981, 1984 and undated) (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Reverend Canon Dick Gillett Labor Day sermon, (2004 Sept 5) (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - September 11th memo and article, (2001 Sept) (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Shop stewards training materials Local 11 1990s, (undated) (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Steward Update publications, (1993-2000) (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Summit Rodeo campaign, (1998) (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Hotels and Their Workers: Room for Improvement report, (2002 Sept) (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - United Auto Workers Grievance Handlers' and Bargainers' Pocket Guide, (undated) (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - USC Fast 1999, (1998-1999) (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Wilhelm mailings, (1998 and 1999 Aug-Dec) (Box 15, Folder 43 and 45)
    - Wilhelm mailings, (1999 Jan-1999 Jul) (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Wilhelm mailings, (2000-2001) (Box 16, Folder 1 - 3)
    - Wilshire Plaza, (1992 Sept 24) (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Subseries 1.4: Maria Elena Durazo files, 1989-2008
    The bulk of Maria Elena Durazo files document the International Workers Freedom Ride (IWFR) in 2004. Includes ephemera, photographs, and a small number of planning materials, press clippings, and video recordings. Additionally, there is a small amount of materials related to Durazo's campaign run for Local 11 president.
    The files are arranged alphabetically by file title.
    - Article re: David Koff, (2001 Jan 7) (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Button collection, (undated) (Box 53)
    - Certificates of honors, (2002 Jan 18, 2003 Sept 20) (Box 53, Folder 2)
      City of Los Angeles proclamation for Immigration Workers Freedom Ride Day; California Assembly Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride resolution; and others.
    - Civic participation, (undated) (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Comprehensive New Otani documents, (undated) (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Dolores Huerta article, (2004 Fall) (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Durazo 2000 election for president Local 11 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Durazo campaign for Local 11 president 1994 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Georgia Association of Black Elected Officials Proclamation, (2003 Sept 29) (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Guide for Training Facilitators of IWFR Participants, (undated) (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - HERE IU Convention (43rd) opening remarks Immigration Forum and Introductions of Speakers, (2001 Jul) (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - HERE Local 11 general meeting - oversize collage of photographs (first meeting), (1989 June) (Box 55)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride video (VHS), (2003) (Box 50)
      Segments: Rev James Lawson, Freedom Rides Then and Now; Houston IWFR Kick-Off Event 6/14/03; and Rev James Lawson, Organizing Freedom Rides.
      Audiovisual materials require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. All requests to access special collections material must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride Documentary Project: Scenes from the IWFR video (VHS), (2004 March 6) (Box 50)
      Audiovisual materials will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. All requests to access special collections material must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride ephemera, (2003) (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride flyer and poster (3 copies), (2003) (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride photographs and CD, (undated) (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing audiovisual materials. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride photographs, (2004) (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride, (2003) (Box 17, Folder 36)
      Draft of Durazo's remarks, ephemera, logistic information, and song lyrics.
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride clippings packet, (2003) (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride Coalition meeting schedule, (2004) (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride contacts host city, (2003) (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride FAQ, (2003 Sept 8) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride itinerary and action roles, (2003) (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride journals, (2003) (Box 18, Folder 6)
      Printed diary-like entries from a small number of individuals who participated in the IWFR.
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride letter head, (undated) (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride love letters, (2003) (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Mostly opposition emails.
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride media and clippings, (2003) (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride press and materials, (2003) (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride programs, (2003) (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride thank yous and support, (2003) (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Jan Perry IWFR photographs, (circa 2004) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - John Gaddini union pins (2 items) with letter, (2005) (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Know Your Rights training documents, (undated) (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Legislation, (2003 and undated) (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Letter to John Wilhelm from John Lewis, (2003 Feb 21) (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Los Angeles Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride DVD (2 copies), (2003) (Box 50)
      Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing audiovisual materials. All requests to access special collections material must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
      - The Los Angeles Immigration Workers Freedom Ride 2003 TRT 49', 2004; yrlsc_2325_050_001; Carranza, Sylvia; LA Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride Coalition; 1 Video Recordings (1 DVD; Duration: 0:53:46) (Box 50, Case 1)
        CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are available for access. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
    - Los Angeles Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride photograph album, (2003 Sept-Oct) (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Maya Entertainment, (2008 Jun 23) (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - New American Freedom Summer information, ([2004]) (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - News clippings, (2001-2003) (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - New Otani flyers and ephemera, (1994, 1996) (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - News clippings and flyers about Maria Elena Durazo, (1989-1993, 1997-1998, 2001, 2013) (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Non-violence literature, (undated) (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Ontario Federation of Labor (O.F.L.) Toronto video (VHS), (2003 June 14) (Box 50)
    - Out of the Shadows: A Story from the Heart of Working America video (VHS), (undated) (Box 50)
    - Political education and interfaith resources, (2003) (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Robin (Brown) Rodriguez button collection, (undated) (Box 53)
    - T-shirts and book bag (10 items), (2003 and undated) (Box 54)
    - Texas state flag and certificate from Texas House of Representatives presenting flag to Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride (Box 56)
    - USC poverty placard, (1995 Jun 15) (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Worker injuries, (2008) (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 1.5: News clippings, 1994-2013
    The bulk of the news clippings focus on Local 11 activities on behalf of employees employed in Southern California hotels and restaurants. Clippings are mostly from the La Opinión and Hoy, and to a lesser degree from the Los Angeles Times, The Los Angeles Business Journal, and Rafu Shimpo, among others. Much of the clippings were compiled by a union member identified as Carlitos.
    Clippings are arranged in a loose chronological order.
    - English and/or Spanish language news clippings, (1994-1997) (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - English and/or Spanish language news clippings, (1997-2000) (Box 2, Folder 1-5)
    - English and/or Spanish language news clippings, (2001-2003) (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
    - English and/or Spanish language news clippings, (2004-2006) (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - English and/or Spanish language news clippings, (2006 Jan-2006 Dec) (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
    - English and/or Spanish language news clippings, (2006-2007) (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
    - English and/or Spanish language news clippings, (2007-2013) (Box 7, Folder 6-11)
    - English and/or Spanish language news clippings, (2008, 2010-2012) (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
    - Hotel solidarity visits news clippings, (2004-2005) (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
    - United Farm Workers English and/or Spanish news clippings, (2006 Jan) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 1.6: Photographs and ephemera, 1970s, 1991-2004, 1999, circa 2008
    Photographs consist primarily of a Local 11 photograph album and USC Hunger strike scrapbook. The ephemera includes an injury quilt top-like banner created by service workers, a poster, two T-shirts, and empty binder created for Hotel Employee and Restaurant Employees International Union AFL-CIO, CLC
    Files are in original order.
    - County of Los Angeles Federation of Labor, AFL-CIO - Certificates of Affiliation for Local 531, 1971, 1973-76, 1978-79 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Housekeeper injury quilt-top created by service workers, (ca. 2008) (Box 52)
      Appears to have been used in LAANE Century Boulevard campaign.
      Conditions Governing Access
      Special handling required for viewing. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
    - Local 11 photograph album, (1991-2004) (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Local 11 USC Hunger Strike/Fast scrapbook, (1999) (Box 49)
    - Photograph collage of unidentified union members and events (oversize item), (undated) (Box 55)
    - Posters that appear related to Local 11, (1970s and undated) (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - T-shirts (2 items), (1999 and undated) (Box 54)
      AFL-CIO National Convention Los Angeles, California October 11-13, 1999; and Union Jobs Better L.A.
    - Hotel Employee and Restaurant Employees International Union AFL-CIO, CLC (empty binder), (undated) (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Series 2: Local 814 Records, 1950-2003
  The series consists of materials related to the work of Unite Here Local 814. Included are files from UNITE HERE leaders Bill Granfield, Kurt Petersen, Victor Valenzuela, and Tom Walsh, photographs, and ephemera. Files document union supported events such as the Tourism Industry Development Council's (TIDC, later known as LAANE) Santa Monica Living Wage and LAX hotel organizing campaigns; efforts on behalf of employees from Southern California hotels such as Miramar Sheraton, Loews, Airport Marina, Viscount, Holiday Inn LAX, and the Manhattan Beach Radisson, among others; and legal matters involving the NLRB. The files may include magazine and newspaper clippings, a small amount of court case documentation, anti-union literature published by employers, shop steward training materials, union flyers and publications, photographs, and ephemera. Some materials, particularly the clippings, are in Spanish.
  Series is arranged into the following subseries:
  Subseries 2.1 Kurt Petersen files (circa 1980s-2004)
  Subseries 2.2 Tom Walsh files (circa 1980s-circa 1990s, 2001)
  Subseries 2.3 Bill Granfield files (1988-1997, 1999)
  Subseries 2.4 Victor Valenzuela files (circa 1950s-1993)
  Subseries 2.5 Gary Guthman files (1988-1990)
  Subseries 2.6 Photographs and ephemera (1996-2002)
  - Subseries 2.1: Kurt Petersen files, circa 1980s-2004
    Kurt Petersen materials consist of anti-union material, assorted clippings and articles, ephemera, a small number of files related to union efforts on behalf of employees from Southern California hotels such as Miramar and Loews, among others, and LAANE's living wage campaign.
    Files are arranged alphabetically by file title.
    - 502 Colorado project, (1999 Jan) (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - 9/11 tourism workers relief center applications, (2001) (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Access, (1996) (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Access letters, (1995-1997) (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Action Dirty Laundry skit, (undated) (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Action Santa Monica, (2000) (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Anti-union buster resolution, (2000 Jun 27) (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Anti-union consult Luz, (1995, 1997, 2000, undated) (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Anti-union consultant Restrepo, (1986, 1989-1990) (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Anti-union Miramar reports, (1997, 2003-2007) (Box 10, Folder 77)
      Report on the Miramar Sherator Election Hearing (held December 15, 1997); and Cruz and Associates Inc. reports.
    - Anti-union Miramar Sheraton, (undated) (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Anti-union propaganda Darth Vader skit, (undated) (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Anti-union propaganda Loews, (1997, 2000, undated) (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Anti-union propaganda Miramar, (1997-1998) (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Araceli Chinchilla, (1997-1999) (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Aramark contract 1998-2001, (undated) (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Articles, (2000) (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Articles about Miramar Hotel election, (1997 Sept) (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Atlanta Journal-Constitution article and Santa Monica media list, (2000) (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Bloom labor fundraising: Cope executive board contact information, (1998 Jul 24) (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Boycott flyers, (2000s) (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Buy Union Buy American sticker, (undated) (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Certification letters, (2000 Nov) (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - City council staff report, (1994) (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Clergy, SMART, and CLUE press, flyers, and correspondence with restaurants, (2001 and undated) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Clippings and ephemera, (1994) (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Contract '99 fight flyers, (undated) (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Cruz and Associates (Loews Santa Monica Beach Hotel settlement agreement), (2000 Aug) (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Current standards Avion, (1999 Jul 1-2003 June 30, 1999 Aug 1-2002 Jul 31, and 2000 Oct 16-2003 Oct 15) (Box 10, Folder 71)
      Collective bargaining agreements between Manhattan Beach Marriott Hotel and Local 814; Furama Hotel and Local 814 (2 copies); and Hacienda Hotel, Inc. and Local 814.
    - Death penalty event Miramar, (1997 Apr) (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Decibel levels Santa Monica, (2000) (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Delmi Falla - suspension Miramar, (1996-1997) (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Democratic Governors Association conference, (1997 May) (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Democratic National Convention pamphlets for delegates, (2000) (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Democratic National Convention week Santa Monica Loews Hotel, (2000) (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Demographics, (2000, 2004) (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - DFS - LAX, (1999-2000) (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - DFS letter and airport workers article, (2000 Jan 12, 2000 Feb) (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - El Paseo Cafe and Ogden flyers, (undated) (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Election article, (1997 Dec 15) (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Election materials 1996, (undated) (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Election propaganda, (2002) (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Election stipulations, (2000 and undated) (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Election training, (2000 Nov 15) (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Elizabeth incident, (1997-1998) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Fair Political Practices Commission 1995-1996 Campaign Disclosure Information Manual B, (undated) (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Fairmont agreement minibar, (2003 Dec 1) (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Fairmont celebration photographic contact sheets, (undated) (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Fairmont face flyer, (undated) (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Fairmont Miramar, Santa Monica Spanish contract, (undated) (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Fairmont Miramar final contract, (2000) (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Fairmont negotiations, (2000) (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Fujita settlement, (1999) (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Hacienda Hotel kitchen schedules, (1996) (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Health insurance comparisons, (1996, 1998, 2000-2001) (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - HERE convention in Santa Monica, (2001) (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - HERE history, (undated) (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - HERE Labor Organization Annual Report LM2 form, (1990) (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - HERE mail-outs, (undated) (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Hyatt information, (1995) (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Immigration Sheraton, (1997) (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - INOC originals (Loews Santa Monica Beach Hotel), (1997, 2000, undated) (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Interstate 98 publication, (1998 May-Jul) (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Ioga trial transcript with Miramar Sheraton appeal to NLRB., (undated) (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Jewish Federation Annual Meeting Program, (1998 June 28) (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Jobs with Justice, Proposition 208, and Workers' Rights Board handouts, (undated) (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - L.A. Times Nazi article, (1997 Sept 26) (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - La Opinion, The Outlook, and Our Times articles, (1996-1998) (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - LAX 96 and TIDC proposals, (undated) (Box 11, Folder 28)
      One-page list of top 10 reasons to organize LAX and one-page budget related to TIDC support organizing.
    - LAX food service workers action, (1995) (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - LAX Host Marriott organizing, (1999) (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - LAX management information, (undated) (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Legal recourse for undocumented workers, (undated) (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Living wage, (2001) (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Living wage campaign, (2002) (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Living wage clippings, (1998-2001) (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Living wage clippings and flyers, (2000) (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Living wage frequently asked questions and election policies, (1997, 1999-2000) (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Living wage law (letter from P.F. Chang's), (2001 May 25) (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Living wage LAX, (1999) (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Living wage materials and clippings, (1999) (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Living Wage Study Proposal for Santa Monica, California, (1999 Dec) (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Local 814 labor organization annual reports, (1990-1997) (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Lodging forecast, (2000) (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Loews, (undated) (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Loews, (2000-2001) (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Loews articles, letters and flyers, (2000-2002) (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Loews / Legal, (2000) (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Loews / NLRB, (2001-2002) (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Loews and AFMA, (2000-2001) (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Loews and living wage clippings and flyers, (1996, 1998-2000, 2004, undated) (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Loews anti-union consultant reports, (2000-2001) (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Loews card check, circa 2002 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Loews Democratic National Convention clippings, (2000) (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Loews employee manual, (1996) (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Loews Hotel Santa Monica clippings, (2000) (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Loews immigration case, (2002 Mar) (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Loews living wage letter from CLUE, (2001 June) (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Loews NLRB, (2001) (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Loews NLRB settlement agreement for posting, (undated) (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Loews organizing committee booklet and form letters, (2000 and undated) (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Loews subcontracting, (2000-2001) (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Mackron trial, (undated) (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Making State and Local Laws by Richard G. McCracken, (1996) (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Materials from non-violence training by Reverend James Lawson, (undated) (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - MBE Inc. contract, (1993) (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Membership polls, (1991 Dec 12) (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Michael Feinstein, (undated) (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Miramar, (1994-1999) (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
    - Miramar: Araskoge letter, (1998 Jan 31) (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Miramar banquet employees, (1998-1999) (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Miramar client information- news clippings and NLRB, (1990s) (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Miramar clippings, (1997-2000) (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Miramar clippings and flyers, (1994, 1997-1999 and undated) (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Miramar contract 1994-2004 and employee rates, (2000 and undated) (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Miramar contract survey, (undated) (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Miramar contracts, (1988, 2000) (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Miramar current, (1998-1999) (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Miramar Delmy Falla briefs, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Miramar election, (1997) (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Miramar election community event hearing, (1997) (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Miramar election objection briefs, (1998) (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Miramar Grille Restaurant closure negotiations, (2000) (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Miramar hearing transcript, subpoena information, and summons, (1998) (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Miramar Hotel Santa Monica, (1998-1999) (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Miramar Hotel Santa Monica union flyers, (1999) (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Miramar insurance fight, (2000) (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Miramar / Legal, (1994-1998 and undated) (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
    - Miramar / Legal, (1994-1999) (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
    - Miramar / Legal, (1995, 1999) (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Miramar negotiations, (2000 and undated) (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Miramar - NLRB, (1993-1999) (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Miramar - NLRB, (1997-1998) (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
    - Miramar - NLRB, (1998, 1999, 2001) (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
    - Miramar NLRB / Legal, (1996-1999 and undated) (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Miramar NLRB charges against employer, (1997) (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Miramar NLRB ruling, (2001) (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Miramar organizing, (1996-1997) (Box 12, Folder 19)